// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question: "It is defined as something that can be weighed and takes up space.",
    answer: "Matter",
    options: [
      "Molecule",
      "Matter",
      "Volume",
      "Mass"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "It is  used to classify the chemical properties of materials.",
    answer: "Pure substances and mixtures",
    options: [
      "Coulombs Law and Gauss' Law",
      "Kinetic Molecular Theory",
      "Pure substances and mixtures",
      "Matter and Density"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Anything that has mass and takes up space.",
    answer: "Matter",
    options: [
      "Density",
      "Volume",
      "Crystalline Solids",
      "Matter"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "True or False: In general, Matter can exist in four states: liquid, solid, gaseous, and plasma",
    answer: "True",
    options: [
      "True",
      "False",
      ".",
      "."
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "True or False: The universe is not a matter. ",
    answer: "False",
    options: [
      "True",
      "False",
      ".",
      "."
    ]
  },
    { 
    numb: 6,
    question: "It is made up of tiny atoms.",
    answer: "Matter",
    options: [
      "Crystalline Solid",
      "Matter",
      "Amorphous solid",
      "Rubic's Cube"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 7,
    question: "True or False: not all energy is made up of matter. ",
    answer: "True",
    options: [
      "True",
      "False",
      "maybe",
      "I'm not sure"
    ]
  },
    { 
    numb: 8,
    question: "True or False: Matter is not something we can see, hear, feel, touch, or taste. ",
    answer: "False",
    options: [
      "True",
      "False",
      "maybe",
      "I'm not sure"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 9,
    question: "True or False: Matter has its own mass and takes up space.",
    answer: "True",
    options: [
      "True",
      "False",
      "maybe",
      "I'm not sure"
    
    
    ]
  },
    { 
    numb: 10,
    question: "True or False: We can categorize matter based on its physical and chemical properties.  ",
    answer: "True",
    options: [
      "True",
      "False",
      "maybe",
      "I'm not sure"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 11,
    question: "True or False:  Different kinds of matter have different kinds of atoms.",
    answer: "True",
    options: [
      "True",
      "False",
      "maybe",
      "I'm not sure"
    ]
  },
    { 
    numb: 12,
    question: "True or False: The density and inertia of all matter are the same.",
    answer: "False",
    options: [
      "True",
      "False",
      "maybe",
      "I'm not sure"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 13,
    question: "True or False: The interparticle force or the intermolecular force is what draws matter particles together. ",
    answer: "True",
    options: [
      "True",
      "False",
      "maybe",
      "I'm not sure"
    ]
  },
    { 
    numb: 14,
    question: "True or False: Atoms that have protons, neutrons, electrons and a nucleus consist of matter. ",
    answer: "True",
    options: [
      "True",
      "False",
      "maybe",
      "I'm not sure"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 15,
    question: "Both living and non-living entities are made out of what?",
    answer: "Matter",
    options: [
      "Luffy",
      "Volume",
      "Density",
      "Matter"
    ]
  },
]